certapay.com 2004-12-08

# INTERAC Email Money Transfer - Privacy Statement

|  | 

## Privacy Statement

This Privacy Statement, which applies to Canada, describes how Acxsys Corporation and its CertaPay Division (collectively, the "Corporation", "we" or "us") collect, use and disclose personal information of visitors to our website and of individuals with whom we deal offline ("you" or "your"). 

### Your Personal Information 

The Corporation does not request your personal information. You can visit our website without telling us who you are or revealing any personal information about yourself, unless you voluntarily choose to provide it by contacting and corresponding with us via the “contact us” link: https://www.certapay.com/en/contactUs/index.html . 

### How We Use and Disclose Your Personal Information 

If you contact us and voluntarily provide us with your personal information, we may use it for the purposes for which it was provided, namely to establish your identity and respond to your questions, comments or concerns. Please do not include any of your banking or other financial information in your communications with us. 

If you advise us that your query relates to a particular participant in the Corporation's services we may, unless you instruct otherwise, disclose the personal information you provide to us to that participating organization so that they may respond to you directly. 

### Consent 

By providing us with your personal information, you consent to our collection, use and disclosure of that information as described in this Privacy Statement as amended from time to time or as described at or before the time of collection, use or disclosure, as the case may be. If you do not want your personal information to be collected, used or disclosed in this manner, then please either (1) do not submit your personal information to us, or (2) exercise opt-out procedures described above or as may be offered at the time of co lection. If you have submitted personal information to us and wish to withdraw your consent to its retention, use or disclosure, please send an e-mail to [privacymanager@certapay.com ](mailto:privacymanager@certapay.com). You may withdraw your consent, subject to legal or contractual restrictions and reasonable notice. Where permitted or required by law, the Corporation may collect, use or disclose your personal information without your knowledge or consent. 

### Retention of personal information 

We may retain a log of the personal information you voluntarily provide for the purpose of ensuring that your inquiry is adequately dealt with. The Corporation will destroy, erase or render anonymous personal information no longer required for the stated purposes or for a legal or legitimate business requirement. 

### Security Safeguards 

The Corporation takes precautions to protect your personal information against unauthorized access, disclosure, inappropriate alternation, and misuse. Access to your personal information is restricted to those employees of the Corporation whose job responsibilities require them to have access. The precautions taken to protect your personal information include physical, organizational, and technological measures. However, given that electronically transmitted data is not 100% secure, we make no warranties as to the security of any information that you submit electronically, which you do at your own risk. 

### Website Aggregate Data 

The Corporation website logs certain information of visitors to our site, namely the IP address, the type of Internet browser and operating system used, and the domain name of the website or advertisement from which the visitor linked to our site (if applicable). This information is aggregated and logged, and used to measure statistical information about usage of the site, including but not limited to the total number of visits, average time spent on the site, and pages viewed, both in real-time, and within a certain historical time frame. The Corporation uses this aggregated information to measure the use of our site and to improve the content and usage of our site. 

### Other Websites 

The Corporation website contains links to other websites owned and operated by third parties. The third parties who operate these sites may treat the collection, use and disclosure of personal information differently than we do. This could be the case even for those websites which may be framed by this website. We therefore encourage you to review the privacy policies of these websites before disclosing your information to any third party. The Corporation is not responsible for the data collection, use and disclosure practices of companies or organizations to which our website may provide links. 

### How to Access or Correct Your Personal Information 

When required in responding to your enquiries, the Corporation will establish and maintain a file of the personal information that you provide to us, for the purposes described in this Privacy Statement as amended from time to time or as described at or before the time of collection, use or disclosure, as the case may be. Your file will be kept by the Corporation and will be accessible at CertaPay, a division of Acxsys Corporation, 55 University Avenue, Toronto, Ontario. Only the Corporation employees, agents and mandataries who need to access your file in the course of their duties will have access to your file. 

If the Corporation has your personal information on file and you wish to request access to, or correction of, your personal information, please write to Privacy Manager at CertaPay, a division of Acxsys Corporation, 55 University Avenue, Toronto, Ontario M5J 2H7. Some information may not be accessed in certain circumstances, for example if it contains ersonal information of other persons or for legal reasons. To protect your privacy, we will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting you access to, or making corrections to, your personal information. 

### Changes to this Privacy Statement 

This Privacy Statement was last updated on April 30, 2004 and the Corporation may change this Privacy Statement from time to time. If the Corporation makes a material change, this Privacy Statement will be updated accordingly and the revised version will be posted on our website in a timely manner. We recommend that you review this Privacy Statement periodically so that you are aware of any changes. 

### Contact for Further Information 

If you have any inquiries, requests or complaints regarding this Privacy Statement, please send an e-mail to Privacy Manager at [privacymanager@certapay.com ](mailto:privacymanager@certapay.com). 

|  |   
  
|
